<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Basic Physics and Quiz</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="derivation">Physics derived from Ancient Greek word: φυσική (ἐπιστήμη), translit. physikḗ (epistḗmē),
        lit. \'knowledge of nature\', from φύσις phýsis "nature" is the natural science that studies matter and its
        motion and behavior through space and time and that studies the related entities of energy and force.Physics is
        one of the most fundamental scientific disciplines, and its main goal is to understand how the universe behaves.
    </string>
    <string name="MotionDefinition">> Change in position of a body with respect to a stationary object is known as
        Motion.
        \n
        \n
        > We can easily see a movement of a body if it moves fast but it becomes difficult to see the motion of a body
        if it moves very slow.
    </string>
    <string name="uniform">> When a body travels equal distances in equal intervals of time then the body is said to be
        in Uniform Motion.It does not matter how small the intervals are.\n
        >The graph of uniform motion is a straight line.
        \n
        \n
        > When a body travels unequal distances in equal intervals of time then the body is said to be in Non-uniform
        Motion.\n
        >The graph of non-uniform motion is a curved line
    </string>
    <string name="distance">> Distance travelled by a body is the actual length of the path covered by a moving body.\n
        > Distance is a scalar quantity
    </string>
    <string name="displacement">> The shortest distance between the initial and final position of body,alongwith
        direction is known as Displacement.\n
        >Displacement is a vector quantity
    </string>
    <string name="speed">> The distance travelled by the body in unit time is known as the rate of motion or Speed.\n
        > The SI unit of speed is m/s.\n
        > Speed of an object can be obtained by dividing the Distance travelled by time taken.\n
        > Speed= Distancetravelled/Timetaken\n
        > A body is said to be in uniform speed if it covers equal distances in equal intervals of time.
    </string>

    <string name="velocity">> If a quantity specifies the direction of motion along with its speed.It is known as
        Velocity.\n
        > SI unit of velocity is same as that of speed.\n
        > velocity= Displacement/Timetaken
    </string>
    <string name="accelr">> Acceleration of a body is defined as rate of change of its velocity with time.
        \n
        > The SI unit of acceleration is "meter per second square" or m/s<sup>2</sup> ms<sup>-2</sup>.\n
        > When a body is moving with uniform velocity then its acceleration will be zero. \n
        > Acceleration = Final velocity - Initial velocity/Time taken\n
        > if "u" is initial velocity and "v" is final velocity and "t" is time taken then acceleration "a" is given by\n
        a=v-u/t
    </string>
    <string name="forcedef">> A push or pull in a body is called Force.\n
        > Motion generated in an object is because of an action of a Force.
        \n
        > Force is capable of changing the speed of a moving body.\n
        > Force can stop a moving body.\n
        > Force can change the direction of a moving body.\n
        > We can move a stationary body by applying force.\n
        > We can decrease the speed of an object by applying force in the direction opposite to the direction of
        motion.\n
        > A Force can change the shape of an object.\n
    </string>
    <string name="balance">> If resultant of all the forces acting on a body is zero,the forces are called balanced
        forces.\n
        > If the resultant of all the forces acting on a body is not zero,the forces are called unbalanced forces.
    </string>
    <string name="firstlaw">> In an inertial frame of reference, an object either remains at rest or continues to move
        at a constant velocity, unless acted upon by a force.\n
        > If a ball is lying on the ground it will not move by itself or in other words it cannot change its position of
        rest by itself unless acted by an external force.Thus the position of the ball is changed by an external force
        which supports the first law.\n
        > Inertia is that property of a body due to which it resists the change in its state of rest or motion.\n
        > Greater force will be needed to bring a change in the state of a body whether it is in rest or motion,if
        inertia is greater.\n
        > Mass is measure of inertia of body,it means that heavier objects have more inertia than lighter objects.\n
        > we have observed that when a car stops suddenly the passengers fell forward or when it starts suddenly,the
        passengers fall backward.
    </string>
    <string name="momentum">> The product of mass and velocity of a body is known as momentum.\n
        > <i>p=m×v</i> where p=momentum,m=mass and v=velocity.\n
        > Momentum is a vector quantity.\n
        > SI unit of momentum is kg.m/s or kg.m s<sup>-1</sup>.

    </string>
    <string name="second">> In an inertial frame of reference, the vector sum of the forces F on an object is equal to
        the mass m of that object multiplied by the acceleration a of the object: F = ma. (It is assumed here that the
        mass m is constant).\n
        > This law gives relationship between Force and acceleration.\n
        > F=ma can also be written as a=F/m.
    </string>
    <string name="thirdlaw">> When one body exerts a force on a second body, the second body simultaneously exerts a
        force equal in magnitude and opposite in direction on the first body.\n
        > The gun recoils because when a bullet is fired the force sending the bullet forward is equal to the force
        sending the gun backward.But the gun being heavy moves only a small distance and gives a backward kick to the
        soldier.
    </string>
    <string name="conserve">> This law states that,when two or more bodies act upon one another their total momentum
        remains constant or in other words we can say that momentum is never created or destroyed.
    </string>
    <string name="work">> We say work is done when a force produces motion.\n
        > Work = Force × Distance moved\n
        > W=F × S where W=work done,F=force and s = Distance\n
        > Work is a scalar Quantity.\n
        > Unit of work is Newton metre which is written as Nm.This unit is called joule.\n
        > The necessary condition for force to do work is that it should produce motion in the body.\n
        > If a man pushes a stationary wall and applies force,the work done in this case is zero as there is no
        displacement.
    </string>
    <string name="workg">> Whenever we do work against gravity then the work is equal to the product of weight of the
        body and the vertical distance through which the body is lifted.\n
        > When we lift a ball from the ground,we do work against the force of gravity.\n
        > Work done in lifting a body = Weight of the cosy × Vertical distance.\n
        > W=m × g × h where W=work done,m=mass,g=acceleration due to gravity and h=height through which body is lifted.

    </string>
    <string name="energy">> The ability to do work is known as energy.\n
        > The energy is consumed,whenever work is done.\n
        > Energy is a scalar quantity.\n
        > The units of work and energy is same.The SI unit of energy is joule.
    </string>
    <string name="kinetic">> The energy of a body due to its motion is called kinetic energy.\n
        > A runner possesses kinetic energy due to its motion.\n
        > Similarly a moving car has kinetic energy due to its motion.\n
        > So, we can say that every object which has speed has kinetic energy.\n
        > Kinetic energy= 1/2mv<sup>2</sup> where m=mass,v=velocity\n
        > We can say that the kinetic energy of a body is directly proportional to its mass as indicated by the
        formula/\n
        > The kinetic energy of a body is directly proportional to the square of velocity or speed of the body.\n
        > on approaching a hilly road,the driver increases the speed of the car to give it kinetic energy so that it can
        overcome the force of gravity.
    </string>
    <string name="potential">> The potential energy of a body is defined as energy possessed by it due to its position
        or change in shape.\n
        > A body may possess potential energy even when not in motion.\n
        > Potential energy=m × g × h where m=mass,g=acceleration due to gravity,h=height of the body.\n
        > The sum of potential energy and kinetic energy is called mechanical energy.
    </string>
    <string name="power">> The rate of doing work is known as power.\n
        > The work done per unit time is known as power.\n
        > In other words,power is the rate at which energy is consumed.\n
        > Power is a scalar quantity.\n
        > p=w/t where p=power,w=work,t=time
        > The SI unit of power is watt.
    </string>
    <string name="def">> Physics can be defined as the study of nature and natural phenomenon.</string>
    <string name="physicsandmath">> Mathematics is the language of physics.Without the knowledge of mathematics it is
        very difficult for us to study the physics.But it should be noted that mathematics itself is not physics.if we
        are poor at grammar then we cannot communicate with others,same applies to physics,if you are poor at
        mathematics then you cannot understand physics.So if you want to study the physics,then you should learn
        mathematics first.
    </string>

    <string name="gravity">> Every object is attracted towards the center of the earth and the force responsible for the
        attraction is known as force of gravitation of earth or gravity of earth.\n
        > It is gravity that holds the atmosphere above the surface of earth;for falling of rain and it is gravity that
        holds us firmly on the ground.\n
        > If the masses of the objects are small,then the gravitational force which they exert on one another is small
        and we cannot see its effect.For example two stones lying on the ground exert force on one another but due to
        small size we cannot see its effect.\n
        > If one of the object is very massive then the gravitational force becomes very large and its effect can be
        seen easily.For example a ball lying on some height and the earth exert force on one another but due to large
        size of earth the balls down towards the ground.\n
        > According to Newton every object in this universe attracts another object with a certain force known as
        gravitational force.
    </string>
    <string name="lawofgravity">> Universal law of Gravitation was given by Newton.According to universal law of
        gravitation:Every body in this universe attracts every other body with a force which is directly proportional to
        the product of their masses and inversely proportional to the square of distance between them.\n
        > The expression for universal law of Gravitation is F=Gm<sub>1</sub>×m<sub>2</sub> /r<sup>2</sup> Where G is a
        constant known as universal gravitational constant.\n
        > The above formula gives gravitational force between two bodies having mass m<sub>1</sub> and m<sub>2</sub> and
        placed at a distance of r.This formula can be applied anywhere in the universe.\n
        > The value of G has been found to be 6.67×10<sup>-11</sup> Nm<sup>2</sup>/Kg<sup>2</sup>/\n
        > If the distance between two bodies is doubled the gravitational force becomes one forth and if the distance is
        halved then the force becomes four times.\n
        > The force of gravitation is a vector quantity.
    </string>
    <string name="freefall">> In Newtonian physics, free fall is any motion of a body where gravity is the only force
        acting upon it. \n
        > The acceleration of an object which is in freefall does not depend on the mass of the object.\n
        > If feather and the coin are dropped at the same time in a jar having no air in it or we can say that their is
        a vacuum in the jar,and when the coin and the feather are dropped at the same time from the top of the jar,it is
        found that both the coin and the feather will hit the bottom
        of the jar at the same time.This shows that Acceleration of an object which is under freefall is same for all
        bodies or in other words we can say that it does not depend on the mass of the freely falling bodies.
    </string>
    <string name="mass">> Mass of a body is defined as the quantity of matter possessed by it.\n
        > Mass is a scalar quantity.\n
        > SI unit of mass is Kilogram denoted by Kg.\n
        > Mass of a body is constant and does not change from place to place.\n
        > Mass of a body can never be zero.\n
        > Mass of a body is denoted by m.
    </string>
    <string name="weight">> The mass of a body is defined as the force with which it is attracted towards the centre of
        the earth.\n
        > SI unit of weight is newton denoted by letter N.\n
        > W=mg where W is weight of the body ,mass is mass and g is acceleration due to gravity.\n
        > The weight of 1kg mass is 9.8 newtons.
    </string>
    <string name="waves">> A wave is a disturbance in an medium which carries energy from one point to another point.\n
        > It is created by the vibration of particles of the medium through which it passes.\n
        > The medium itself does not move along the wave,only the particles of the medium vibrate about their fixed
        positions.
    </string>
    <string name="longitudinal">> A longitudinal wave is that wave in which the particles of the medium vibrate back and
        forth in the same direction in which wave is moving.\n
        > The sound waves are longitudinal waves.\n
        > When vibrating particles move forward they push and compress the air and create a region of high pressure in
        other words we can say that the particles of the medium are closer to each other,this is called compression.\n
        > When the vibrating particles move backward,a region of low pressure is created or in other words we can say
        that the particles of the medium are farther apart,this is known as rarefaction.\n

    </string>
    <string name="transverse">> A transverse wave is a moving wave that consists of oscillations occurring perpendicular
        (right angled) to the direction of energy transfer (or the propagation of the wave).\n
        > The waves that are formed on the surface of water in a pond are transverse waves.
        > The hump in transverse wave is known as <b>Crest</b>.This part is above the line of zero disturbance.\n
        > The depression in a transverse wave is known as <b>Trough</b>.This part is below the line of zero
        disturbance.\n
    </string>
    <string name="vibration">> The to and fro or back and forth motion of an object is known as vibration.\n
        > In human beings sound is produced by larynx also known as voice box.\n
        > You can easily feel the vibration by keeping hand on your throat.
    </string>
    <string name="prod">> In humans,the sound is produced by voice box also known as <b>Larynx</b>.\n
        > It is at the upper end of the windpipe.\n
        > Two vocal cards are stretched across the larynx in such a way that it leaves a narrow slit between them for
        the passage of air and in this way the sound is produced.\n

        > The vocal cards in men are about 20mm long and in women it about 15mm long this is the reason that the
        men,women and children have different voices.
    </string>
    <string name="ears">> The ear is the part through which we hear.\n
        > The shape of the outer part of ear is like a funnel and when sound enters in it,it keeps going down the canal
        at the end of which a thin membrane is stretched known as <b>eardrum</b>.\n
        > The ear drum acts like a stretched rubber sheet.Sound vibrations makes it vibrate.The vibrations are send to
        inner ear and from there signal goes to brain and that is how we hear.\n
    </string>
    <string name="sound">> Sound is a form of energy that makes us hear.\n
        > Sound travels in the form of waves.\n
        > Sound waves are longitudinal waves.\n
        > When vibrating particles move forward they push and compress the air and create a region of high pressure in
        other words we can say that the particles of the medium are closer to each other,this is called compression.\n
        > When the vibrating particles move backward,a region of low pressure is created or in other words we can say
        that the particles of the medium are farther apart,this is known as rarefaction.\n
    </string>
    <string name="chara">> Wavelength is the minimum distance in which a wave repeats itself.We can also define it as
        the distance between the two consecutive compressions and rarefactions.\n
        > Wavelength is usually denoted by Greek letter lambda(λ).\n
        > The SI unit for measuring wavelength is metre(m).\n
        > <b>Amplitude</b> can be defined as the maximum displacement of particles of the medium from their original
        positions when a wave passes through it. \n
        > It is represented by A.\n
        > To describe the size of the wave,the term amplitude is used.\n
        > Time period is defined as the time taken to complete one vibration.\n
        > The unit is seconds and represented by T.\n
        > <b>Frequency</b> is defined as number of vibrations per second.\n
        > The SI unit of frequency is Hertz written as Hz.\n
        > The frequency of a wave is represented by f.
    </string>
    <string name="elec">> <b>Charge</b> is something which the body possesses that make them capable of exerting the
        electric force and responding to it.\n
        > Charges are responsible for the electric force.\n
        > The SI unit of electric charge is Coulomb(C).
    </string>
    <string name="conservec">> Total charge of an isolated system always remains constant or conserved.\n
        > Charges can be created or destroyed in equal and unlike pairs only.For example a Neutron turns into an
        electron and proton.But these electron and proton have opposite charges and are equal.So the total charge before
        and after remains zero.\n
    </string>
    <string name="current">> The charges constitute the current when they are flowing through a conductor.\n
        > The current is expressed by a unit known as Ampere(A).\n
        > Ammeter is the instrument that measures the electric current.\n
    </string>
    <string name="conduct">> <b>Conductors</b> are those bodies which allow the charges to pass through them.\n
        > All conductors have some loosely bound electrons and are free to move.These electrons are called free
        electrons.These electrons allow the charge to flow through conductor.\n
        ><b>Insulators</b> are those bodies which do not allow the current to pass through them.For example glass.\n
        > These substances have practically no free electrons.
    </string>
    <string name="electricpotential">> Electric potential at a point is defined as amount of work done in bringing a
        unit positive charge from infinity to that point.\n
        > Charge flows in a circuit due to the difference in potential between the two bodies in contact.\n
        > The device that measures the potential difference is known as voltmeter.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ohm">> This law states that under same physical conditions,the electric current flowing through a
        metallic wire is directly proportional to the potential difference across the ends of the conductor.\n
    </string>
    <string name="superc">> Those substances whose resistance becomes zero at low temperature are called super
        conductors and the phenomenon is called super conductivity.\n
    </string>
    <string name="funda">> Those quantities which are chosen for measuring fundamental quantities are known as
        fundamental quantities e.g. kilogram,metre etc.\n
    </string>
    <string name="deri">> Those quantities which are expressed in terms of base quantities e.g. unit of speed is ms<sup>
        -1</sup>.
    </string>
    <string name="solar">> Solar system consists of the sun and all the celestial bodies which revolve around it.\n
        > There are eight planets in our solar system which are arranged in order of their distance from the sun they
        are:Mercury,Venus,Earth,Mars,Jupiter,Saturn,Uranus and Neptune.\n
        > <b>Inner planets</b> are first four planets:Mercury,venus,Earth,Mars.\n
        > <b>Outer planets</b> include Jupiter,saturn,uranus and Neptune.
    </string>
    <string name="emit">> The stars are giant balls of Hydrogen gas.\n
        > The temperature of the center of the star is from 2Million to 5 Million degree celsius.\n
        > At this temperature their occurs fusion,hydrogen gas fuses together to give <b>Helium</b> with the liberation
        of huge amount of heat and energy.
    </string>
    <string name="sun">> The sun is the nearest star to our earth.\n
        > Our sun is a medium sized star.\n
        > The distance of the sun from the earth is 150 million kilometers.
    </string>
    <string name="impterms">> <b>Light Year</b> is the distance travelled by the light with the speed of 300000 km/s in
        one year.\n
        > <b>Light Minute</b> is the distance travelled by the light at a speed of 300,000 km/s in one minute.\n
        > <b>Alpha Centauri</b> is the nearest star after sun to Earth located at a distance of 4.3 light years.\n
        > All heavenly bodies appear to move from east to west because the earth rotates on its north-south axis from
        west to east.\n
        > <b>Constellations</b> are group of stars that form a recognisable shape.\n

    </string>
    <string name="planets">> <b>Planets</b> are heavenly bodies that revolve around the sun in a well defined orbit.\n
        > There are eight planets in our solar system.\n
        > The path of the planet is known as <b>Orbit</b>.\n
        > The position of the planets with respect to earth changes everyday.\n
        > <b>Mercury</b> is the nearest planet to the sun.\n
        > Mercury is one of the hottest planets in the solar system because it is nearer to sun.\n
        > <b>Venus</b> is the second planet from the sun.\n
        > Venus is the brightest star.\n
        > Venus rotates from east to west.\n
        > <b>Earth</b> is the only planet in solar system on which life exists.\n
        > Moon is the only natural satellite of earth.\n
        > <b>Mars</b> is the fourth planet in order of the increasing distance from the sun.\n
        > Mars is known as Red planet.\n
        > There are two moons revolving around it.\n
        > <b>Jupiter</b> is the largest planet in the solar system.\n
        > The gravitational pull of this planet is very high due to large size.\n
        > <b>Saturn</b> is surrounded by three flat rings.\n
        > There are 30 moons revolving around the Saturn.\n
        > Titan is the largest moon in the solar system.\n
        > <b>Uranus</b> is the third largest planet in the solar system.\n
        > 21 moons are revolving around uranus.\n
        > <b>Neptune</b> is the eight planet from the sun in order of the distance.\n
        > 21 satellites are discovered around it.\n
    </string>
    <string name="comets">> A <b>comet</b> is a star-like object with a long tail and the length of the tail grows as it
        comes nearer to the sun.\n
        > <b>Halley\'s comet</b> appears after 76 years.It is expected to visit us in 2062.\n
        > <b>Meteors</b> are also known as shooting star.\n
        > A meteors enters our atmosphere and catches fire due to the friction of atmosphere.\n
        > <b>Meteorites</b> are those meteors that reach our earth.\n
    </string>
    <string name="light">> Light is an electromagnetic wave that produces in us the sensation of vision.\n
        > <b>Luminous objects</b> are those objects that have light of their own like sun.\n
        > <b>Non-Luminous objects</b> are those objects that don\'t have light of their own,they reflect the light from
        luminous objects like moon.\n
    </string>
    <string name="charlight">> Light passes through transparent objects like glass,but cannot pass through opaque
        objects like wood.\n
        > The path of the light is a straight line.\n
        > Light is reflected when it falls on smooth surfaces like mirror.\n
        > The speed of light is maximum in vacuum.\n
        > The speed of light in vacuum is 3 ×10<sup>8</sup> ms<sup>-1</sup>.
    </string>
    <string name="implight">> <b>Medium</b> is a substance through which light propagates.It is of three types as listed
        below:\n
        > <b>Transparent medium</b> is that type of medium through which light can propagate like glass.\n
        > <b>Translucent medium</b> is that type of medium through which light passes partially like paper.\n
        > <b>Opaque</b>is that type of medium through which light cannot pass like iron.\n
        > <b>Ray</b> is defined as the straight path along which the light travels in a medium.\n
        > <b>Beam</b>:When a number of rays are combined together a Beam is formed.
    </string>
    <string name="reflect">> When a ray of light strikes a surface then the ray of light bounces back in the same
        medium.This phenomenon is known as reflection of light.\n
        > Reflection is of two types:\n
        > <b>Diffused reflection</b> is reflection from rough surface.\n
        > <b>Regular Reflection</b> is reflection from smooth surface.\n
    </string>
    <string name="lawsofreflect">> The angle of incidence(i) is equal to angle of reflection.\n
        > The incident ray,the reflected ray and the normal at the point of incidence all lie in same plane.\n
        > Image formed by a plane mirror is always virtual and erect.
    </string>
    <string name="refraction">> When a ray of light travelling in one medium enters into another medium their occurs
        bending of light at the surface of separation of two media.This is known as Refraction.\n
        > <b>Optically denser</b>  medium is that medium in which the speed of light is less.\n
        > <b>Optically rarer</b> medium is that medium in which the speed of light is more.
    </string>
    <string name="lawsofrefract">> The incident ray,the refracted ray and the normal to the interface of separation at
        the point of incidence all lie in same plane.\n
        > The ratio of sine of angle of incidence to the ratio of sine of refraction is a constant.This law is also
        known as Snell\'s law.
    </string>
    <string name="instru">> Altimeter: Measures altitude of an aircraft.\n
        > Accelerometer: Measures acceleration.\n
        > Ammeter: Measures electric current in ampere.\n
        > Barometer: Measures Atmospheric pressure.\n
        > Calorimeter: It is used to measure heat in chemical reaction.\n
        > Fathometer : It is used to measure Depth.\n
        > Galvanometer: It is used to measure electric current.\n
        > Hydrometer:Measures specific gravity of liquid.\n
        > Hygrometer: It is used to measure atmospheric humidity.\n
        > Inclinometer:Measures angel of slope.\n
        > Lactometer:Measures purity of milk.\n
        > Ohmmeter:Measures resistance.\n
        > Odometer:Measures distance.\n
        > Radar:It is used to detect distant objects.\n
        > Spectrometer:Measures light spectrum.\n
        > Voltmeter:Measures volt.
    </string>
    <string name="magnetic">> The Electromagnetic effect was first discovered by Oersted.\n

    </string>
    <string name="natural">> <b>Natural magnets</b> are the one,which occur naturally e.g.,lodestone.\n
        > <b>Artificial magnets</b> are prepared artificially by magnetising small pieces of iron.\n
    </string>
    <string name="lines">> Michael Faraday was the one that put forward the concept of Magnetic field lines.\n
        > Faraday told us that the magnet modifies the space around itself in such a fashion that if any other magnetic
        substance moves into this space it experiences a force.The region is termed as magnetic field of the magnet.\n
        > Magnetic field line can be best described as the pictorial representation of magnetic field.\n
        > The magnetic field lines travel from north to south pole of magnet outside the magnet and from south to north
        pole inside the magnet.\n
        > They are continuous closed curves. \n
        > They do not intersect each other.\n

    </string>
    <string name="source">> Energy is ability to do work.It can exist in many forms.Some of them are:\n
        > Heat energy\n
        > chemical energy\n
        > Electrical energy\n
        > Nuclear energy\n
    </string>
    <string name="renewable">> <b>Renewable</b> sources are those sources which are inexhaustible.e.g. solar energy.\n
        <b>Non-renewable</b>
        sources are exhaustible and should be used wisely.e.g. coal.
    </string>
    <string name="coal">> Coal is a mixture of carbon,hydrogen,oxygen, nitrogen and sulphur.\n
        > It was formed by decomposition of plants that got buried under the surface of earth millions of years ago.\n
        > Carbonisation is a process of conversion of wood into coal at high temperature and pressure.
    </string>

    <string name="wind">> Wind possesses kinetic energy and therefore and therefore can be used as a source of energy.\n
        > Winds blow because of uneven heating of earth\'s surface.\n
        > Wind energy is used to operate
        <b>Wind mills.</b>
        > It is clean and pollution free source of energy.
    </string>
    <string name="solare">Solar energy is produced by solar rays.\n
        > The solar energy recieved by the earth is in scattered form or diffused form.\n
    </string>
    <string name="geothermal">It is heat energy present inside the earth.\n
        > Geothermal plants use the heat energy of the magma.\n
        > It is renewable source of energy and is free of cost.\n
    </string>
    <string name="nuclearenergy">> This energy is released in the process of fission or fusion.\n
        > The nuclear energy is used to generate heat which is then used in steam turbines to produce electricity.\n
    </string>


    <string name="awards">Henri Poincaré Prize\n
        Hoyle Medal and Prize\n
        Abdus Salam Award\n
        Arthur L. Schawlow Prize in Laser Science\n
        Walter Schottky Prize\n
        Simon Memorial Prize\n
        Sloan Fellowship\n
        Albert Einstein Award\n
        Infosys Prize\n
        Isaac Newton Medal\n
        R W B Stephens Medal\n
        Swan Medal and Prize\n
        Thomson Medal and Prize\n
        Three Physicists Prize\n
        VASVIK Industrial Research Award\n
        Wolf Prize in Physics\n
        Fluid Dynamics Prize (APS)\n
        Foresight Institute Feynman Prize in Nanotechnology\n
        List of Fritz London Memorial Prizes\n
        Hector Memorial Medal\n
        Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics\n
        Dannie Heineman Prize for Mathematical Physics\n
        EPS Europhysics Prize\n
        Faraday Medal and Prize\n
        Nobel Prize in Physics\n
        ASA Gold Medal\n
        Frank Isakson Prize for Optical Effects in Solids\n
        James Clerk Maxwell Prize in Plasma Physics\n
        James C. McGroddy Prize for New Materials\n
        Rayleigh Medal and Prize\n
        David Richardson Medal\n
        Richtmyer Memorial Award\n
        Robert A. Millikan award\n
        Rumford Prize\n
        Rutherford Medal and Prize\n
        Sakurai Prize\n

        Albert Einstein Medal\n
        Einstein Prize \n
        Albert Einstein World Award of Science\n

        ASA Silver Medal\n
        Hans Bethe Prize\n
    </string>
    <string name="astro">>It is on of the oldest branches of Astronomy.\n
        >Astrophysics is the branch of astronomy that employs the principles of physics and chemistry to ascertain the
        nature of the astronomical objects, rather than their positions or motions in space\n
        > Theoretical astrophysics describes the function of celestial bodies.\n
        > Astrophysicists attempt to describe the properties of dark energy,dark matter and <b>Black holes</b>.\n
    </string>
    <string name="astronomy">>Astronomy is a natural science that studies celestial objects and phenomena.\n
        > In order to explain the origin of the celestial bodies, their evolution, and phenomena, the different
        disciplines of science such as physics, chemistry, mathematics are applied.\n
        >Astronomy is categorised as below:
        > Observational astronomy is focused on acquiring data from observations of astronomical objects, which is then
        analyzed using basic principles of physics. \n> Theoretical astronomy is oriented toward the development of
        computer or analytical models to describe astronomical objects and phenomena. The two fields complement each
        other, with theoretical astronomy seeking to explain observational results and observations being used to
        confirm theoretical results
    </string>
</resources>